btimes.com.my 2014-02-14

# Business Times

## For MEDIA PRIMA DIGITAL

### 1\. PRIVACY STATEMENT

1.1 For the purposes of Privacy Policy, unless the context provides otherwise, the following words shall have the following meaning:-

"You" shall mean any user of all or any of the Digital Services.

“Media Prima Digital” shall mean the subsidiary of Media Prima Berhad, i.e. Alt Media Sdn Bhd (Company No. 272025-V) that operates the Websites (as defined herein) and providing the Digital Services (as defined herein). 

“Digital Services” shall mean the following services provided by Media Prima Digital:

(a) the video streaming service via Tonton that encompasses the digital streaming of recorded free-to-air television programmes of TV3, 8TV, ntv7 and TV9 (all of which are the affiliates of Media Prima Digital) and any other syndicated content ; 

(b) the service that encompasses the provision of printed contents (daily and weekend newspapers, tabloids and magazines published by the News Straits Times Press (M) Sdn Bhd (Company No. 4485-H)–an affiliate of Media Prima Digital) in digital format;

(c) other related services i.e. managing the online lifestyle and entertainment portal known as “GUA” (as detailed herein), website maintenance for affiliated companies, online research and analytics and these related services include future products and/or services offered by Media Prima Digital on the Websites.

"Media Prima Berhad Group" shall mean any subsidiary and affiliate companies of Media Prima Berhad (Company No. 532975-A).

“Third Parties” shall mean the partners, affiliates, service providers, contractors, agents and third party suppliers with whom Media Prima Digital or affiliated companies under Media Prima Berhad Group enter into agreements from time to time and persons with whom they may contract in order to provide the Digital Service.

"Personal Information" or "Personal Data" shall mean personal data as defined in the Malaysian Personal Data Protection Act 2010.

“Websites” means the following websites currently managed by Media Prima Digital as well as new websites to be created, developed and managed by Media Prima Digital from time to time in the future: 

(a) Alt Media Sdn Bhd (http://www.altmedia.com.my/); 

(b) TonTon (http://www.tonton.com.my/); 

(c) NSTP e-Media Sdn Bhd (http://www.emedia.com.my/); 

(d) GUA (http://www.gua.com.my/); 

(e) Affiliated television operators’ websites i.e. http://www.tv3.com.my, http://www.8tv.com.my, http://www.ntv7.com.my and http://www.tv9.com.my; 

(e) Affiliated FM radio operator’s websites i.e. http://www.hotfm.com.my, http://www.flyfm.com.my and http://www.onefm.com.my; 

(f) The BigTree Outdoor Sdn Bhd website (http://www.bigtreeoutdoor.com.my); 

(g) Affiliated print websites i.e. http://www.hmetro.com.my, http://www.bharian.com.my and http://www.nst.com.my; 

(h) The New Straits Times Press (Malaysia) Berhad Group website (http://www.nstp.com.my/); and 

(i) Media Prima Bhd (http://www.mediaprima.com.my).

“Authorized Representative” means the duly-appointed official representative of Media Prima Digital whose name and contact e-mail address are made available on each of the Websites under the “Contact Us” link.

1.2 The following statement explains Media Prima Digital’s Privacy Policy ("this Privacy Policy") regarding the personal information collected by Media Prima Digital about you. 

1.3 In order to use the Website, upon registration and from time to time, you will be asked to submit personal information about yourself as name, identity card number, billing [if applicable], permanent address, e-mail address, phone, fax and other information. You would also need to provide your credit card number and all related information for billing purposes [if applicable]. By providing Media Prima Digital with your details in the fields requested, you enable Media Prima Digital to provide you with the Digital Service. We will treat such personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This privacy policy covers Media Prima Digital and the Website and its related channels.

1.4 The Digital Service is provided to you subject to the Website Terms of Use and in accordance with the laws of Malaysia. Media Prima Digital will act in accordance with the Malaysian Personal Data Protection Act 2010 in this Privacy Policy.

1.5 Unless otherwise stated to the contrary and for the purposes herein, all words and expressions shall have the same meaning as in the Website Terms of Use.

1.6 By submitting your information, you consent to the use of your personal information collected by Media Prima Digital, in the manner as set out in this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to the collection and/or processing of your personal information other than in relation to the advertising and marketing of any product or service of Media Prima Digital and the Media Prima Berhad Group, Media Prima Digital cannot process your personal information and approve the same for registration purposes. 

### 2\. TYPE OF INFORMATION MEDIA PRIMA DIGITAL COLLECTS 

2.1 Personal Information

2.1.1 Media Prima Digital collects and uses your personal information (i.e. personal information which identifies you such as, your name and residential or postal address, date of birth, gender, telephone and fax numbers, email address, and credit/debit card information [if applicable]; lifestyle and interests) only with your knowledge and consent when you use the Website or the Digital Service, make use of our product and service enquiries, or when you respond to communications from Media Prima Digital (such as contests, questionnaires or surveys) and other information collected on registration or through surveys.

2.1.2 When you request pages from the Website server, it automatically collects some information about your preferences, including your internet protocol (IP) address. Media Prima Digital uses this for account management and to help diagnose problems with the Website server, to administer the Website and for the purposes set out in Section 3 below.

2.2 Non-personal Information 

2.2.1 Media Prima Digital may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browsers you use or the website from which you linked to the Website. Media Prima Digital may also aggregate details which you have submitted to the Website (for example, your age and the town where you live). You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist Media Prima Digital in providing an effective service on the Website. No personally identifiable information is gathered during the use of the Website except for information given by you via e-mails, which is in a secure portion of the Website.

2.2.2 If at any time the Website offers any e-mail, feedback or forum facilities, Media Prima Digital may collect the information, which you disclose. Such information will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

2.2.3 When you access the Website, Media Prima Digital’s web servers will automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser (explained further in Section 6).

2.3 Third Party Information.

2.3.1 Media Prima Digital does not monitor or permanently store third party information save for the purpose of accounting, billing [if applicable] or record keeping, or unless required by law.

### 3\. USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION 

3.1 The personal information provided in your application to register for the use of the Website and, if relevant, for subscription to Digital Service, including any additional information you may subsequently provide, may be used and processed by Media Prima Digital for the following purposes:- 

• assessing your application to register for the use of the Website; 

• to technically administer the Website and conduct internal activities; 

• to create user profiling and preferences and verify and record your personal particulars including comparing it with information from other sources and using the information to communicate with you; 

• to provide services to you and respond to your inquiries; 

• to manage and administer your participation in contests; 

• to undertake market surveys, market research and development, statistical and trend analysis; 

∧ To be used as deemed necessary by Media Prima Berhad across its multiple media platforms. 

• to provide you with information on products and services of Media Prima Digital and the Media Prima Berhad Group; and/or 

• such other purposes as set out in the Website Terms of Use. 

3.2 In relation to direct marketing, subject to due acknowledgement of your request by the Authorized Representative, you may request Media Prima Digital by written notice not to process your personal information for the purpose of advertising or marketing via phone, post, email or mobile text message or whatever means any product or service of Media Prima Digital and/or the Media Prima Berhad Group;

3.3 If Media Prima Digital wishes to use your personal information for new purposes, this will, from time to time, be updated in this Privacy Policy and Media Prima Digital will offer you the means to withhold your consent to those new purposes by sending an email to [Media Prima Digital](mailto:contactus@altmedia.com.my).

3.4 As part of the products or services offered to you through the Website, the information you provide to Media Prima Digital may be transferred to countries outside of Malaysia. By way of example, this may happen if any of Media Prima Digital’s servers are from time to time located in a country outside of Malaysia or one of Media Prima Digital’s service providers is located in a country outside Malaysia. If Media Prima Digital transfers your information outside of Malaysia in this way, Media Prima Digital will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected. In addition, if you use Media Prima Digital’s services while you are outside Malaysia, your information may be transferred outside Malaysia in order to provide you with those services.

3.5 Media Prima Digital may receive personal data about you from third parties. In such event, Media Prima Digital may add this data to the data Media Prima Digital already received from you for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

### 4\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

4.1 Media Prima Digital does not share with others any personal information that you provide to Media Prima Digital through the Website, except with your consent or as described in this Privacy Policy.

4.2 Subject to the opt-out choices that you may have made when you provided Media Prima Digital with such information, Media Prima Digital may share your personal information with the Media Prima Berhad Group. If Media Prima Digital shares your personal information with the Media Prima Berhad Group, your personal information will become permanently subject to the information use and sharing practices of the Media Prima Berhad Group, and any subsequent opt-out election that you make with Media Prima Digital will not affect the Media Prima Berhad Group's ability to send you promotional materials or share your information.

4.3 Media Prima Digital may share personal information that you provide to Media Prima Digital through the Website with the Third Parties. In turn, the Third Parties may share this personal information with their affiliates and with service providers whom they engage to perform services related to the Website or the operation of Media Prima Digital’s business. Examples of these services include website operation, membership processing and authorisation, credit or debit card processing [if applicable], authorisation and payments [if applicable], currency conversions [if applicable], fraud protection and risk reduction, product and service customization, advertising and program promotional material distribution, data and trend analysis and, where applicable, data maintenance and cleansing. The Third Parties are authorized to use this personal information only in connection with the services they are engaged to perform.

4.4 Except as set out in this Privacy Policy, Media Prima Digital will not disclose any personally identifiable information without your permission unless Media Prima Digital: 

• is legally entitled or required to do so (for example, if required to do so by legal process or advice or for legal proceeding or the exercise of any functions conferred by law); or 

• believes that such release is necessary to protect and/or defend Media Prima Digital’s rights, title or interest including the Website and the rights, title or interest of Media Prima Digital’s users, Third Parties, customers or others; or

• believes in good faith that the law or legal process requires it for the administration of justice; Media Prima Digital has received a valid administrative request from a law enforcement agency or court; or 

∧believes that such release is necessary for medical purposes; Media Prima Digital has received a valid request for a healthcare professional; or 

∧believes that such release is necessary for employment purposes; Media Prima Digital has received a valid request for disclosure from your current or potential employer; or 

• believes that the user is harming or interfering with other users of the Digital Service, anyone else, or violating the Website Terms of Use / subscription agreement [if any], or infringing any of Media Prima Digital’s legal rights.

4.5 In addition to the foregoing and notwithstanding anything to the contrary under this Privacy Policy, Media Prima Digital shall not be liable to you or to any other person in respect of any personal information processed: (a) in pursuance of a non-commercial transaction; (b) that falls under Credit Reporting Agencies Act 2010; (c) outside of Malaysia; and (d) for use by any person or entity not established in Malaysia.

4.6 In the event of a sale of all or most of the assets of Media Prima Digital, this information may be transferred to the purchaser.

4.7 Media Prima Digital may share non-personal information with its marketing partners, advertisers and others from time to time. Examples of such non-personal information include the number of users who visited the Website during a specific time period. This information generally is shared in an aggregated form.

### 5\. THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

5.1 The Website may contain, from time to time, links to other web sites. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to information gathered through these other websites. 

5.2 Media Prima Digital cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites even if: 

• you accessed the third party website using links from the Website; or 

• you linked to the Website from a third party website. 

Media Prima Digital recommends that you check and read the policy of each and every site you visit and contact the owner or operator of such website if you have any concerns or questions.

### 6\. COOKIES 

6.1 Media Prima Digital may store some information (commonly known as a "cookie") on your computer when you log in to the Website. The Website is able to read these cookies for information purposes when you revisit the Website. The type of information Media Prima Digital collects as a result of a cookie being accepted by you is specific to your personal computer and includes the internet protocol (IP) address, the date and time the personal computer visited the Website, what parts of the Website were looked at and whether the web pages requested were delivered successfully. This information is anonymous; it represents a computer rather than a person.

6.2 Media Prima Digital uses the cookie information to improve its knowledge of the use of the Website and to enable Media Prima Digital to be able to ascertain whether the Website is operating at an optimal level. This allows Media Prima Digital to enhance its web offerings to you and to provide an enjoyable and an innovative online experience.

6.3 These cookies do not permanently record data and they are not stored on your computer's hard drive. Once you close your browser, the cookie is deleted. You can erase or block this information by changing the settings on your computer (please refer to your help screens or manuals). If you do erase or block this information you may not be able to utilise some features of the Website.

6.4 Some of Media Prima Digital’s business partners may use cookies on the Website (for example, links to business partners). Media Prima Digital does not want its business partners to use cookies to track the Website’s users' activities once they leave the Website. However, Media Prima Digital may not have total control over how its business partners may use cookies on the Website. If you become aware that Media Prima Digital’s business partner is placing an unwanted cookie on your hard drive, please contact Media Prima Digital to assist Media Prima Digital in resolving the problem.

### 7\. CHOICE, CHANGE, UPDATE OF AND ACCESS TO YOUR INFORMATION 

7.1 There are several ways in which you can tell Media Prima Digital whether or not you want to receive promotional communications from us. At certain locations on the Website, you will have choices to opt-out or opt-in to receive various types of communications. You will need to have your user ID and password. You will have an opportunity to make or change your selections in this regard. You also will have an opportunity to change these selections by clicking on an "unsubscribe" hyperlink contained in promotional emails Media Prima Digital sends you or by emailing [Media Prima Digital](mailto:contactus@altmedia.com.my).

7.2 There is also a link that you can click if you wish to correct, change or update your particulars in your Digital Service’s membership / account. 

7.3 You may terminate and close your Digital Service’s membership / account by emailing directly to [this address](mailto:contactus@altmedia.my). Your e-mail must specify your user ID, and expressly state that you wish to terminate your Digital Service’s membership / account. Termination may take up to seven (7) working days.

7.4 You can write to Media Prima Digital at any time to obtain details of the personal information Media Prima Digital holds about you. Please write to: 

Media Prima Digital c/o 

Alt Media Sdn Bhd   
3rd Floor, North Wing, Sri Pentas   
No. 3, Persiaran Bandar Utama   
Bandar Utama  
47800 Petaling Jaya  
Selangor Darul Ehsan  
Malaysia

You are required to include your name, address, user ID and Digital Service’s membership / account number. Please also let Media Prima Digital know on what information you want a copy of your personal data.

7.5 Media Prima Digital reserves the right to refuse to provide its users with a copy of their personal information, but will give reasons for such refusal.

### 8\. DATA RETENTION

8.1 Your Personal Data can be retained until three (3) months from the date you notify Media Prima Digital of your wish to deactivate the Digital Service’s membership / account, and may be retained in either a physical or electronic format. Upon the expiry of the aforementioned period, your personal data shall be securely and permanently deleted from Media Prima Digital’s database.

### 9\. SECURITY

9.1 Security measures, including Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology, are in place in order to protect personal information that Media Prima Digital collects from unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. The said personal information will be stored and backed up securely in an environmentally-controlled location. Only authorized people with user ID and password from Media Prima Digital have access to the information. All Media Prima Digital’s employees and data processors, who have access to and are associated with the processing of personal information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your Digital Service’s membership / account information.

9.2 You are advised to log off from your Digital Service’s membership / account, clear your cache and close the browser window after use so as to minimise any risk on the user ID and password being compromised. You are further advised not to reveal your user ID and password to others. If you become aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of your user ID and password, please send an email to [Media Prima Digital](mailto:contactus@altmedia.com.my).

### 10\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

10.1 From time to time, Media Prima Digital may make changes to this Privacy Policy. If Media Prima Digital makes any substantial changes to this Privacy Policy and the way in which it uses your personal data Media Prima Digital will post these changes on this page and will do its best to notify you of any significant changes. Please check this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. If this Privacy Policy changes in any way, it will be updated on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are updated on the information which is collected, how it is used and under what circumstances, if any, it is shared with other parties.

_**This Privacy Policy was last updated on 27 March 2013**_
